MARK MUNTER

PROFILE

I have more than 5 years of experience in banking and have held leadership roles during that time. I've been recognized numerous times for my excellent customer service. I am currently working on expanding my skillset to include Salesforce.

EXPERIENCE

Bank Sales and Service Contact Center Representative, USAA — 2020-Present

I specialize in helping the military community and their families with every facet of their banking needs, including opening accounts, fraud verification and problem solving.

Intern, Accenture — 2019-2020

Studied Salesforce and ServiceNow with Accenture leads.

Member Care Specialist, Firstmark Credit Union — 2018-2019

I assist Firstmark members with questions on their account as well as updating them of any new policies and/or member benefits. I also offer relevant products as necessary.

Citigold Service Specialist, Citibank — 2016-2018

I used my knowledge of our systems and polices to handle the issues of Citibank's most influential customers. I assisted customers and other service specialists with researching payments, tech support, and fraud.

Meter Technician, Corix — 2015-2016

I inspected and upgraded electrical meters as a subcontractor for CPS Energy.

Substitute Teacher, S.A.I.S.D. — 2014-2015

I helped students control their behavior with positive and appropriate techniques. I also supervised and ensured students' safety.

Emergency Case Manager, B.C.F.S. — 2014-2015

Deployed in response to emergency disaster relief. Managed cases processed paperwork and was trained to handle interviews.

Lead Teller, IBC Bank — 2012-2014

I processed cash transactions, made schedules and audited my tellers' cash inventory. I was responsible for making sure my staff met their sales quotas. I was also responsible for handling any issues that required escalation.

EDUCATION

2010

B.A. HISTORY

UNIVERSITY OF TEXAS-SAN ANTONIO

SKILLS & INTERESTS

Customer Service • Banking • Research • Reading • Tech Support • Excel •

Problem Solving • Learning Salesforce